<resources>
    <string-array name="version_title_list" translatable="false">
        <item>Version: 6.00</item>
        <item>Version: 5.17</item>
        <item>Version: 5.16</item>
        <item>Version: 5.15</item>
        <item>Version: 5.14</item>
        <item>Version: 5.13</item>
        <item>Version: 5.12</item>
        <item>Version: 5.11</item>
        <item>Version: 5.10</item>
        <item>Version: 5.01</item>
        <item>Version: 5.00</item>
        <item>Version: 4.01</item>
        <item>Version: 4.00</item>
        <item>Version: 3.40</item>
        <item>Version: 3.32</item>
        <item>Version: 3.31</item>
        <item>Version: 3.30</item>
        <item>Version: 3.20</item>
        <item>Version: 3.10</item>
        <item>Version: 3.00</item>
        <item>Version: 2.30</item>
        <item>Version: 2.20</item>
        <item>Version: 2.12</item>
        <item>Version: 2.11</item>
        <item>Version: 2.10</item>
        <item>Version: 2.01</item>
        <item>Version: 2.00</item>
        <item>Version: 1.50</item>
        <item>Version: 1.40</item>
        <item>Version: 1.30</item>
        <item>Version: 1.20</item>
        <item>Version: 1.10</item>
        <item>Version: 1.00</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="version_list" translatable="false">
        <item><![CDATA[- Fixed live stream link <br>- Fix for Android 15 <br>- Reduced ads interruptions <br>- Bug fixes & improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Few bugs & improvements! ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Updated to latest libraries for better performance! ]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Even more general bug fixes and improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- More general bug fixes and improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- General bug fixes and improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Fixed astronauts being outdated <br>- Translations for over 100 languages! <br>- Bug fixes & improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Support for Android 14 <br>- Fixed an issue with people in space showing old astronaut list <br> - Translations for few dozen languages <br> - General UI and bug improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Support for Android 13 <br>- Fixed an issue with flyby page <br> - General UI and bug improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Support for Android 12 <br>- Few new features and improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Overhaul of the app to now work with Android 11 <br>- Fixed many issues making the app not work after months of no maintenance <br>- Few new features and improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Notification service compatible with Android 8.0 and above<br>- Fixed crashes with notification service <br>- App name is no longer just \"Map\" on home screen. Yikes! How did this one go through? :thinking_face:]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Big layout changes throughout the app<br>- Save future ISS flybys to your phone calendar<br>- Share the flybys with others]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Map won\'t reset on orientation change<br>- Fixed a crash caused by slow connections]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Crash on start for existing users<br>- What\'s new on Help page (You looking at it silly)]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Small bug fixes<br><br>NOTE: If you already had the app, this update may break your application. For the time being, uninstalling and reinstalling the app will fix the issue]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[HAPPY NEW YEAR FOLKS<br>- Additional settings such as text size and a better support for color picking to support all colors and transparencies<br>- Layout improvements, mostly on settings<br>- Fixed settings descriptions getting cut off on tablets/bigger screens<br>- Updated libraries used by the app<br>- General improvements and bug fixes]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Improved People in Space layout<br>- Astronauts now have links to their Twitter and wiki<br>- Couple of major bug fixes]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- General bug fixes and improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- All activities can rotate<br>- Less memory usage<br>- Small improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Much more customization<br>- Implemented printing of additional info<br>- Map type<br>- ISS no longer force locked<br>- General improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- App much faster / responsive<br>- Updated the Astro info page<br>- Bug fixes &amp; general improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- General bug fixes and improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Updated Help page<br>- New Icon<br>- Improved layout throughout the app<br>- General improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Improved Who\'s in Space<br>- Click Astros for more info<br>- Fix service crashing when having connectivity problems<br>- General improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- General bug fixes and improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Can now access ISS\'s live feed<br>- Improved layout through the app<br>- A small guide for new users<br>- Fixed an issue where services in settings weren\'t updating correctly<br>- General bug fixes and improvements]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- App should respond much faster<br>- Supports API 14 instead of 17<br>- Removed two permissions<br>- General bugs and library updates]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Significantly reduced the app\'s size<br>- Across app visual change<br>- Added more features]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Fixed the layout of loading icon<br>- Fixed a issue where the map would not have loaded on some instances]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Fixed some layout issues on android devices of 4.4 to 4.0]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Fixed an icon issue]]></item>
        <item><![CDATA[- Initial Product<br> - Map view<br> - ISS icon updating with a timer]]></item>
    </string-array>

</resources>