<resources>
    <string name="app_name">ISS Tracker</string>
    <string name="map_activity">Map</string>
    <string name="flybys_title">Passing By</string>
    <string name="help_title">About</string>
    <string name="label_location">Flybys</string>
    <string name="label_people_in_space">On Duty</string>
    <string name="label_setting">Settings</string>
    <string name="label_help">Help</string>
    <string name="label_stream">Live!</string>
    <string name="midAt"> at </string>
    <string name="countryFlagContentDescription">Country flag this astronaut is from</string>
    <string name="astronautTwitterContentDescription">Icon to link to astronauts twitter page</string>
    <string name="astronautWikiContentDescription">Icon to link to astronauts wiki page</string>
    <string name="astronautGoogleContentDescription">Icon to link to astronauts Google search page</string>
    <string name="refreshTitle">Refresh Rate</string>
    <string name="refreshSummary">Amount of time before updating ISS location on map</string>
    <string name="lockTitle">Lock ISS</string>
    <string name="lockSummary">Lock onto ISS and follow it on the map</string>
    <string name="infoTitle">Additional Info</string>
    <string name="infoSummary">Provide additional information about ISS on the map</string>
    <string name="mapTitle">Map type</string>
    <string name="mapSummary">Change the map type</string>
    <string name="decimalTitle">Decimal Places</string>
    <string name="decimalSummary">Change the accuracy of all numerical values</string>
    <string name="sizeTitle">Prediction line size</string>
    <string name="sizeSummary">Change the size of ISSs prediction line</string>
    <string name="textSizeTitle">Text size</string>
    <string name="textSizeSummary">Change the size of all text values on map</string>
    <string name="notificationTitle">ISS Notification</string>
    <string name="notificationSummary">Notify when ISS is expected to fly over my location</string>
    <string name="errorLocation">Unable to find your location.</string>
    <string name="errorPermissionLocation">Denied access to your location</string>
    <string name="nothing_available">There are no ISS passes by your location at this time</string>
    <string name="unable_to_get_astronauts">Unable to get astronauts. Make sure you are connected to the internet and try again later</string>
    <string name="unable_to_get_passes">Unable to get ISS passes. Make sure you are connected to the internet and try again later</string>
    <string name="errorMap">Can not apply settings to map</string>
    <string name="errorFiveTimes">Failed all 5 times. Either you have no connection or server is overloaded.</string>
    <string name="errorLessFive">Request to server failed. Retrying…</string>
    <string name="errorNoWiki"> does not have a wiki page</string>
    <string name="errorNoTwitter"> does not have a Twitter account</string>
    <string name="errorNoInstagram"> does not have a Instagram account</string>
    <string name="errorNoFacebook"> does not have a Facebook account</string>
    <string name="data_corrupted">App data is corrupted. Resetting!</string>
    <string name="polyError">Unable in creating prediction line</string>
    <string name="calendar">Calendar</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="image_content">Image of a map with a marker for user location.</string>
    <string name="iss_sighting_share_title">ISS Sighting</string>
    <string name="iss_sighting_share_description">ISS will be visible here. Going to check it out!</string>
    <string name="iss_sighting_share_body">"Check it out! ISS will be visible at "</string>
    <string name="iss_sighting_share_chooser">Share…</string>
    <string name="on">" on "</string>
    <string name="since">"Launched "</string>
    <string name="license">Open source licenses</string>
    <string name="msg_license">This application is constructed using following software:</string>
    <string name="msg_about_library_description">ISS Tracker is an android application that allows you to track the position of the International Space Station and find out what astronauts are currently in space.</string>
    <string name="desc_about_app">About this app</string>
    <string name="version">Versions</string>
    <string name="version_msg">List of previous changes, fixes, and updates:</string>
    <string name="refresh_stats_every_seconds">Refresh stats every %1$d seconds</string>
    <string name="change_the_thickness_of_the_prediction_line">Change the thickness of the prediction line</string>
    <string name="starts">Starts: %1$s</string>
    <string name="duration">Duration: %1$s</string>
    <string name="ad_attribution">Ad</string>
    <string name="ad_icon">Ad Icon</string>

    <string name="msg_get_it_on_play_store_url" translatable="false">https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.restart.spacestationtracker</string>
    <string name="apache_open_source_url" translatable="false">http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0</string>

    <string-array name="software_list" translatable="false">
        <item>Lottie</item>
        <item>Glide</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="software_url_list" translatable="false">
        <item>https://github.com/airbnb/lottie-android.git</item>
        <item>https://github.com/bumptech/glide</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="app_ID_Main" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1850763013639682~8939815838</string>
    <string name="banner_ad_unit_id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1850763013639682/4298913050</string>
    <string name="interstitial_ad_unit_id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1850763013639682/1377236244</string>
    <string name="locations_native_ad_unit_id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1850763013639682/9845698217</string>
    <string name="on_duty_native_ad_unit_id" translatable="false">ca-app-pub-1850763013639682/4740210185</string>

    <string-array name="entryValues">
        <item>0</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="entry">
        <item>None</item>
        <item>Normal</item>
        <item>Satellite</item>
        <item>Terrain</item>
        <item>Hybrid</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="legal_title">Legal Jibber Jabber</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">Terms of Use</string>

    <string name="privacy_policy_content" translatable="false"><![CDATA[
        <h2>Privacy Policy</h2>
        <p><b>Effective Date:</b> August 28, 2025</p>
        <p>This Privacy Policy describes Our policies and procedures on the collection, use, and disclosure of Your information when You use the Service and tells You about Your privacy rights and how the law protects You.</p>
        <p>We use Your Personal data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, You agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.</p>

        <h3>Interpretation and Definitions</h3>
        <h4>Interpretation</h4>
        <p>The words of which the initial letter is capitalized have meanings defined under the following conditions. The following definitions shall have the same meaning regardless of whether they appear in singular or in plural.</p>
        <h4>Definitions</h4>
        <p>For the purposes of this Privacy Policy:</p>
        <p><b>"Application"</b> means the software program provided by the Company downloaded by You on any electronic device, named Space Station Tracker.</p>
        <p><b>"Company"</b> (referred to as either "the Company", "We", "Us" or "Our" in this Agreement) refers to the developer of the Application.</p>
        <p><b>"Device"</b> means any device that can access the Service such as a computer, a cellphone, or a digital tablet.</p>
        <p><b>"Personal Data"</b> is any information that relates to an identified or identifiable individual.</p>
        <p><b>"Service"</b> refers to the Application.</p>
        <p><b>"Usage Data"</b> refers to data collected automatically, either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).</p>
        <p><b>"You"</b> means the individual accessing or using the Service, or the company, or other legal entity on behalf of which such individual is accessing or using the Service, as applicable.</p>

        <h3>Information We Do Not Collect</h3>
        <p>We do not require you to create an account or provide any personally identifiable information, such as your name, email address, or phone number, to use our Application.</p>

        <h3>Information We Collect and Use</h3>
        <h4>Location Data</h4>
        <p>With your explicit permission, we may collect your device\'s location data (latitude and longitude).</p>
        <p><b>Purpose of Collection:</b> This information is used solely to provide the core functionality of the Application, such as calculating the position of the International Space Station (ISS) relative to you and predicting fly-over times for your specific location. This data is processed on your device and is not stored on our servers. You can enable or disable location services at any time through your Device\'s settings.</p>
        <h4>Usage Data & Advertising</h4>
        <p>We use Google AdMob to display advertisements within the Application. AdMob is a third-party service that may collect and use information to provide personalized ads.</p>
        <p><b>Data Collected by AdMob:</b> AdMob may collect Usage Data, which can include your device\'s unique advertising identifier, IP address, device type, operating system, and information about your interaction with ads. This data is used by Google to serve relevant ads and to measure ad performance.</p>
        <p>We do not have access to or control over the data collected by Google AdMob. We encourage you to review Google\'s Privacy Policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy</p>

        <h3>Permissions Required</h3>
        <p><b>INTERNET:</b> Necessary to fetch data from third-party APIs (e.g., ISS location, astronaut information) and for AdMob to serve advertisements.</p>
        <p><b>ACCESS_FINE_LOCATION / ACCESS_COARSE_LOCATION:</b> Required to access your device\'s location to provide location-specific features, as described above. This permission is optional and only used if you grant it.</p>

        <h3>Third-Party Libraries</h3>
        <p>Our Application uses the following third-party libraries to enhance its functionality:</p>
        <p><b>Glide:</b> An image loading and caching library for Android. Glide may cache images on your device for performance but does not collect personal data.</p>
        <p><b>Lottie:</b> A library for displaying animations. Lottie does not collect personal data.</p>

        <h3>Data Security</h3>
        <p>We value your trust in providing us your information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. However, remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.</p>

        <h3>Children\'s Privacy</h3>
        <p>This Service does not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to take necessary actions.</p>

        <h3>Changes to This Privacy Policy</h3>
        <p>We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted.</p>

        <h3>Contact Us</h3>
        <p>If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at: restartapplication@gmail.com</p>
    ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="terms_of_use_content" translatable="false"><![CDATA[
        <h2>Terms of Use</h2>
        <p><b>Effective Date:</b> August 28, 2025</p>
        <p>Please read these Terms of Use ("Terms", "Terms of Use") carefully before using the Space Station Tracker mobile application (the "Service") operated by us.</p>
        <p>Your access to and use of the Service is conditioned on your acceptance of and compliance with these Terms. These Terms apply to all visitors, users, and others who access or use the Service.</p>
        <p>By accessing or using the Service, you agree to be bound by these Terms. If you disagree with any part of the terms, then you may not access the Service.</p>

        <h3>1. Use License</h3>
        <p>Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the Space Station Tracker app per device for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license, you may not:</p>
        <ul>
            <li>modify or copy the materials;</li>
            <li>use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);</li>
            <li>attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained in the Service;</li>
            <li>remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or</li>
            <li>transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.</li>
        </ul>
        <p>This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by us at any time.</p>

        <h3>2. Disclaimer</h3>
        <p>The Service and the materials within are provided on an \'as is\' basis. We make no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaim and negate all other warranties including, without limitation, implied warranties or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights.</p>
        <p>The data provided by the Service, including but not limited to the location of the International Space Station (ISS), fly-over predictions, and astronaut information, is sourced from third-party APIs and is for informational purposes only. We do not guarantee the accuracy, timeliness, or completeness of this information and are not liable for any errors or omissions, or for any actions taken in reliance thereon.</p>

        <h3>3. Limitation of Liability</h3>
        <p>In no event shall we or our suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on the Service, even if we or an authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage.</p>

        <h3>4. Third-Party Services and Advertisements</h3>
        <p>The Service uses third-party APIs to provide its core functionality and displays third-party advertisements through Google AdMob. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party web sites or services. You further acknowledge and agree that we shall not be responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, for any damage or loss caused or alleged to be caused by or in connection with the use of or reliance on any such content, goods, or services available on or through any such web sites or services.</p>

        <h3>5. Changes to These Terms</h3>
        <p>We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to modify or replace these Terms at any time. We will try to provide at least 30 days\' notice prior to any new terms taking effect. What constitutes a material change will be determined at our sole discretion.</p>
        <p>By continuing to access or use our Service after those revisions become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised terms. If you do not agree to the new terms, please stop using the Service.</p>

        <h3>6. Governing Law</h3>
        <p>These terms and conditions are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of Washington U.S. and you irrevocably submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts in that State or location.</p>

        <h3>Contact Us</h3>
        <p>If you have any questions about these Terms, please contact us at: restartapplication@gmail.com</p>
    ]]>
    </string>
</resources>
